stomping2.com 2011-05-27

# Privacy Policy | Stompernet Blog | Empowering Your Online Success

Since you're new here maybe you'd like to try [StomperNet for $1.00](https://stompernet.infusionsoft.com/saleform/nathnifwu). Thanks for visiting!

StomperNet is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology  
that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This  
Statement of Privacy applies to the StomperNet Web site and governs  
data collection and usage. By using the StomperNet website, you  
consent to the data practices described in this statement. For the  
purpose of this Privacy Statement, the “StomperNet Web Site”  
shall have the same meaning as defined in the StomperNet Terms Of  
Use.

STOMPERNET LLC is committed to best email practices, and has been accredited by  
the Institute for Spam and Internet Public Policy as meeting the  
requirements for listing in their SuretyMail IADB Email Accreditation Program. Our IADB  
registration number is 20070516000566. For more information see

http://www.SuretyMail.com

**Collection of your Personal Information**

StomperNet collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail  
address, name, home or work address or telephone number. StomperNet  
also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique  
to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests  
and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is  
automatically collected by StomperNet. This information can include:  
your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and  
referring Web site addresses. This information is used by StomperNet  
for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service,  
and to provide general statistics regarding use of the StomperNet Web  
site.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable  
information or personally sensitive data through StomperNet public  
message boards, this information may be collected and used by  
others.. Note: StomperNet does not read any of your private online  
communications.

StomperNet encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you  
choose to link to from StomperNet so that you can understand how  
those Web sites collect, use and share your information. StomperNet  
is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web  
sites outside of the StomperNet and StomperNet family of Web sites.

**Use of your Personal Information**

StomperNet collects and uses your personal information to operate the StomperNet  
Web site and deliver the services you have requested. StomperNet also  
uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other  
products or services available from StomperNet and its affiliates.  
StomperNet may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about  
your opinion of current services or of potential new services that  
may be offered. StomperNet may also contact you from time to time via  
your email address to provide you with a variety of information,  
including weekly wrap ups, newsletters, bulletins and similar  
information.

StomperNet does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.  
StomperNet may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external  
business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest  
to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable  
information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not  
transferred to the third party. In addition, StomperNet may share  
data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis,  
send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange  
for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your  
personal information except to provide these services to StomperNet,  
and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your  
information.

StomperNet does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as  
race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit  
consent.

StomperNet keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within  
StomperNet, in order to determine what StomperNet services are the  
most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and  
advertising within StomperNet to customers whose behavior indicates  
that they are interested in a particular subject area.

StomperNet Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice,  
only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that  
such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or  
comply with legal process served on StomperNet or the site; (b)  
protect and defend the rights or property of StomperNet; and, (c) act  
under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users  
of StomperNet, or the public.

**  
Use of Cookies**

The StomperNet Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize  
your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on  
your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run  
programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely  
assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain  
that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience  
feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web  
server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you  
personalize StomperNet pages, or register with StomperNet site or  
services, a cookie helps StomperNet to recall your specific  
information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of  
recording your personal information, such as billing addresses,  
shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same StomperNet  
Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved,  
so you can easily use the StomperNet features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers  
automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser  
setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline  
cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive  
features of the StomperNet services or Web sites you visit.

**  
Security of your Personal Information**

StomperNet secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or  
disclosure. StomperNet secures the personally identifiable  
information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure  
environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.  
When personal information (such as a credit card number) is  
transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of  
encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL)  
protocol.

**Changes to this Statement**

StomperNet will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company  
and customer feedback. StomperNet encourages you to periodically  
review this Statement to be informed of how StomperNet is protecting  
your information.

**Contact Information**

StomperNet welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you  
believe that StomperNet has not adhered to this Statement, please  
contact StomperNet at support@stompernet.com.

We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and  
remedy the problem.
